<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> - Articles</title>
    <description>An accountant who is one step closer to reaching her goals</description>
    <link>
    </link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Reason Why We Need Time Alone</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Our daily activities can sometimes make us stressed and fed up. We get tired of having the same routine every day. From getting up in the morning, prepare to work eight (or more!) hours, traveling to and from work, and spend our meager free time on Netflix or social media until we fall asleep and face the same day tomorrow. Then, when the weekend finally comes, it’s fleeting and before we know it, it’s Monday again!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /qualitytimee-alone</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/qualitytimee-alone</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Take A Break</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever feel stuck in place?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year, I tried so hard to grow to be a better person and take small steps to reach my goals, but I feel like I didn’t make any progress. For two weeks this month, (August 2021) I just lay in my bed (in Indonesia we called it as rebahan), and didn’t want to do anything even thought I already knew exactly what I should do.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /take-a-break</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/take-a-break</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>5 Lessons from 5 Years of Working</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I graduated from university in June 2016 with a bachelor’s degree in Economics. I found it challenging to find a job at that time, especially because I didn’t have any specific goals. My only purpose was to find a job after I graduate, regardless of what it was. I applied to become a banker, a financier, general accounting, anything that was related to my studies.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 04:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /five-years-working-five-lessons</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/five-years-working-five-lessons</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Stop Staying In Your Comfort Zone!</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently interviewed some of my acquaintances about work, and I realized that some of them are choosing to stay in their comfort zone. They told me that they don’t like it if they have to do something new in addition to their regular workload. Here is one of my acquaintance’s story:&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 04:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /comfort-zone</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/comfort-zone</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Do Women Have an Expiration Date?</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I watched a Japanese Drama called &lt;a href=&quot;https://asianwiki.com/Love_and_Fortune&quot;&gt;Love and Fortune&lt;/a&gt; (Koi no Tsuki).  I’ll be briefly outlining the plot, but only so I can emphasize the things I took away from the drama. I identified with a lot that that the main lead went through in the story, and it made me think a lot about my own life and my romances.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 04:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /women-expiry-date</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/women-expiry-date</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Habits, Books, and Personal Growth</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;‘Do you feel like your life is stuck in place? Do you want to change it, and grow to be a better person – to have a beautiful life? What do you want to be?’ - Those questions were always in my head, until recently I got the answer. Yes, I want to change my life and reach my goals. The next question is what step should I take? I realize that if I want to change something, I have to start within myself. Then again, which part should I change first?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 04:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /habit-read</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/habit-read</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Beauty of Sharing</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;When you get your paycheck every month, what will you do first? Transfer to your savings account? Pay your bills? Buy something online?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 14:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /sedekah-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/sedekah-post</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Thank you 2020! Welcome 2021</title>
        
          <description>&lt;h6 id=&quot;2020-a-year-full-of-learning&quot;&gt;2020, A Year Full of Learning&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&quot;2021-a-year-full-of-blessings&quot;&gt;2021, A Year Full of Blessings&lt;/h6&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 18:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /2020-to-2021</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2020-to-2021</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Start Your Gratitude Journal, NOW!</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you complaining about your life? Or are you feeling grateful with what you already have?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 18:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /gratitude-journal</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/gratitude-journal</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>'Got Scammed' Stories</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;BE AWARE, SCAMMER IS EVERYWHERE&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 18:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /scammer</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/scammer</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Overcome Mental Blocks with These Things</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever say to yourself that &lt;em&gt;“you can’t do that”&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;“you don’t deserve it”&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;“you are not worthy”&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;“I don’t want to take any risks”&lt;/em&gt; and so on, then you have mental blocks. Hina Hashmi from Your Life A Practical Guide to Happiness Peace and Fulfilment said, &lt;em&gt;“If you experience any emotion like frustration, hesitation or anger, while planning your dream life, means you need to clear some mental blocks”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 18:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /mental-block</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/mental-block</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>A Blessing in Disguise</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever think about &lt;em&gt;why do you live in this world?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 18:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /blessing-in-disguise</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blessing-in-disguise</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Compound Interest is Magic!</title>
        
          <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-power-of-compound-interest&quot;&gt;The Power of Compound Interest&lt;/h2&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 14:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /compound-interest</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/compound-interest</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Why we should have a Personal Branding?</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Basically, everyone has their own personal branding and what the &lt;em&gt;personal branding&lt;/em&gt; is?  Personal Branding is how a person develops and maximizes his potential or skills, behavior and understands the superior value of what he wants to do and wants to achieve in himself. Honestly, I just found out about the personal branding and it’s important to make people acknowledge your existence.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 14:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /personal-brand</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/personal-brand</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Running Is Our Therapy</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of people think that run is a tiring exercise and need a lot of energy to do that. Yeah, I used to think the same thing, and every time I imagined do a run, I felt my heart suffocating! In the end of 2017, my friend asked me to run together with him and his running group. Actually, I wasn’t interested but because he asked me, I said yes. I ran for 5 kilometers and for me it was so challenging, I couldn’t breath properly, my legs felt heavy to take each step, thirsty, and I just made them ran slowly (because they need to waited for me!).&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 12:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /running</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/running</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Improving Microsoft Excel Skills</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;As an accountant, understanding Microsoft Excel is important because many of my tasks require using spreadsheets (the rest require a specialised accounting system!). Microsoft Excel has grown to become one of the most important computer software applications in workplaces around the world, especially if you work in the Accounting and Finance Department.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /microsoft-excel</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/microsoft-excel</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Online Courses are FUN!</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Since this corona virus outbreak is happening all around the world and forced us to stay at home as well as we can’t go to work made me realized that I need to do something to reach my goals. I never think about online course before, I don’t even know if this course is existing. When I found out my goal to have a remote job and what kind of job I can do so I think Digital Marketing is suitable for me. I love learning about digital world and in this century, we spend almost all of our time on digital such as social media, exploring on google, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /shinas-online-course</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/shinas-online-course</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Quarter Life Crisis</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Perspective of Life&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /shinas-25</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/shinas-25</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Shina's First Experiences with Web Development</title>
        
          <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;markdown-x-html&quot;&gt;Markdown x HTML&lt;/h2&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /shinas-first-experience-with-website</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/shinas-first-experience-with-website</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Shina's First Post</title>
        
          <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;om--swastiastu&quot;&gt;Om  Swastiastu&lt;/h2&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 14:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        /shinas-first-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/shinas-first-post</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
